Why did Cheng An get hurt?
I'm asking you a question.
Why was Cheng An at the winery?
Instead of questioning me,
you should let the police investigate
those fruit farmers causing trouble.
Also,
Aunt Lin, if you're not here to visit the patient,
then please leave.
I'm warning you,
Sang Luo.
Cheng An saved you
only because you're Brother Feng's daughter.
Don't get any funny ideas.
I'm sure
if you were the one injured today,
Little Uncle would have saved you too.
How is he?
Doctor?
The surgery went well.
He's very lucky.
That nail almost pierced his kidney.
If it had, it would've been disastrous.
But the wound is too deep.
Combined with massive blood loss,
he is extremely weak right now.
He needs further observation.
If he can wake up within 48 hours,
he'll be fine.
If he doesn't wake up,
then it's hard to say.
The patient still needs care.
Which of you can stay with him?
Me.
I'll do it.
Little Uncle saved me,
so I'm staying.
What's your reason, Aunt Lin?
Once Cheng An wakes up,
please notify me immediately.
I told you to stir up the fruit farmers.
How did you end up hurting someone?
Now things have gotten out of hand.
If you get arrested,
I won't be able to protect you.
Find a place to lay low for a few days.
I'll arrange for you to go abroad in a few days.
Only this much money?
I can't leave the house.
I still need to eat and drink, right?
This will run out in no time.
Won't I have to go out anyway?
When that time comes,
it won't be good for you if I let something slip,
right?
Listen, don't push your luck.
Take the money, shut your mouth, and get the hell out.
Right away, right away, right away!
Are you done yet?
Right away!
Xiaowei
What's wrong with Cheng An?
What?
Xiaowei
Recently,
Valley Breeze Group's oppression of fruit farmers
has continued to escalate.
It is reported
that the group maliciously breached the ice grape contract.
Many fruit farmers are suffering miserably.
Once the news broke,
it sparked widespread public attention.
Public anger is running high,
and Valley Breeze wine sales have plummeted.
Look at this.
What do we do now?
Mr. Cheng Yan,
you've only been in charge for a few days,
and you've already caused such a huge mess.
How do you plan to resolve this?
Today,
calling everyone to this meeting
is exactly
to find a solution, isn't it?
As for Cheng Yan,
he just wanted to create more profit for the company.
His original intention was good.
It's just that
his methods
were a bit inappropriate.
Exactly.
Before, when the company's profits soared,
wasn't everyone quite happy?
What kind of talk is that?
Valley Breeze Group values long-term interests.
Do we only look at short-term gains?
Mr. Li,
look, didn't you just say it yourself?
We're doing a long-term business.
If our goods can't sell for a while,
isn't that also very normal?
"Can't sell for a while"?
What you're losing now is the group's reputation!
Valley Breeze Group worked hard for decades
to build its current reputation.
And now it's about to be ruined by you!
For this matter,
someone must be held accountable.
Mom,
you said it yourselves,
Cheng Yan just took over the company a few days ago.
In such a short time,
he is unfamiliar with the business processes.
This is completely normal.
Previously, Cheng An managed all operations.
The current industrial adjustments
were also Cheng An's decisions.
That's what led to today's situation.
Madam,
the notice to halt the ice wine business
is clearly signed in black and white
with Cheng Yan's name.
The fruit farmers rioting at the estate
is also because of Cheng Yan.
Instead, Mr. Cheng An
got injured protecting the estate,
and is still unconscious in the hospital.
Are you in such a rush to shift the blame to him?
We must have a clear conscience
in how we conduct ourselves.
Watch out!
Are you okay?
I said I'm fine.
That's good.
It's my fault for getting distracted.
Getting distracted?
At least you know.
Do you know you were wrong?
I really do.
Don't worry.
As long as I'm here,
I won't let you get hurt.
Xiaowei
Little Uncle
You're awake.
I'm Sang Luo.
I'll go get the doctor.
So?
Ready for the next step?
Exposing their wine adulteration scandal.
It's time to begin.
But Cheng An got hurt saving you.
You're not getting soft, are you?
I'm not.
No one can stop my revenge plan.
Recently,
Valley Breeze Group was hit by a wine adulteration scandal,
causing a massive public uproar.
According to reliable sources,
a huge amount of Valley Breeze red wine on the market
is suspected of having severe quality issues.
After random testing by professional agencies,
illegal additives were detected in the latest batch.
Idiot!
Look what you've done!
Mom...
You can't blame this all on me.
Someone is definitely targeting me.
Targeting Valley Breeze.
The stock market reacted drastically.
Valley Breeze Group's stock price
suffered panic selling at the opening bell,
taking a nosedive.
You short-sighted fool!
Are you trying
to ruin your father's and my life's work?
Mom,
I was wrong. I'm sorry.
I really know I was wrong.
I just wanted to do something for the group.
I wanted to save the group some money.
Mom,
please help me one more time, okay?
I'm begging you.
Mom,
help me one more time!
This mess is too big.
Even if I wanted to help you,
those people on the board
won't let you off the hook.
If my eldest were still here,
how could I have possibly
pinned my hopes on you?
Cheng An
Is your injury any better?
I was really worried about you.
Are you saying my injury has nothing to do with you?
I didn't expect you to get caught in the crossfire.
But,
it also proves my worth.
As long as you're willing to work with me,
I'll help you take back
everything in Valley Breeze that belongs to you.
And then what?
Become someone
who, just like you,
stops at nothing to achieve their goals?
What's that supposed to mean?
A partner like you,
is someone I wouldn't dare take on.
Do you have anything else to explain?
Brother Feng and I lost our baby.
I'm hurting more than
any of you.
That was Brother Feng's and my flesh and blood!
We tried for so long
to finally have this baby.
Everyone was so hopeful before he died.
I didn't want to keep it a secret.
But I didn't know how to say it.
The old lady waited so long for a grandson.
How could I just tell her,
"Mom,
I'm sorry.
The baby is gone"?
Xiao An,
please give me a little more time,
okay?
The old lady is in poor health.
I don't want to upset her anymore.
Think carefully about this yourself.
How are you going to explain it to her?
Cheng An,
You have a sharp tongue,
but you still care about me.
After all these years,
you still can't let me go.
Because of the wine adulteration incident,
Valley Breeze suffered huge losses.
The shareholders are investigating Cheng Yan.
He's already been suspended.
His suspension won't recover Valley Breeze's lost profits.
Right now, Valley Breeze is
leaderless.
They desperately need someone to take charge.
It's time for you to go back, right?
There's no rush.
If I rush back now,
people will definitely think I'm
coveting power,
and overly eager.
If the board continues to pressure the old lady,
she'll definitely come to beg me personally.
Going back then
will be the perfect timing.
You're always one step ahead.
By the way, you're just going to let Lin Wanmei off?
Those miscarriage records
are great leverage against her.
If you just leaked them,
wouldn't that kick her out of
the game at Valley Breeze?
Don't be silly.
The situation at Valley Breeze is delicate now.
Even though Cheng Yan has temporarily lost power,
he still has the old lady backing him.
Right now,
it's me,
Cheng Yan,
and Lin Wanmei.
A three-way standoff,
keeping each other in check.
If Lin Wanmei falls,
it'll just be me and Cheng Yan going head-to-head.
As for those old geezers on the board,
there's no telling if they'll side with him.
I'd be completely restricted then,
unable to make a move.
Besides, there are more important things right now.
First, the fruit farmers caused trouble,
which suddenly escalated into violence
and destroying the orchards.
It seems like someone is pulling the strings
and fanning the flames behind the scenes.
Then it was quickly exposed online.
Just when public opinion peaked,
the wine adulteration scandal suddenly broke out.
It really does seem like someone is
fanning the flames behind the scenes.
Exactly.
Things aren't that simple.
Eat your shrimp.
After you finish it,
you have to do me a favor.
Alright, alright, alright.
Leave it to me.
Director Fang,
this is the miserable state of Valley Breeze today.
The stock price has plummeted to this extent.
More than half of our partners have bailed.
If this continues,
the group is really going to be finished.
Director Fang,
you have to come up with a solution.
What else can be done?
Given the current situation,
we still need to find someone
who is familiar with the business,
has industry connections,
and has the prestige to turn the tide.
What are you still hesitating for?
For this role, apart from Mr. Cheng An,
could there be anyone else?
Cheng An is still recovering from his injuries.
With this massive mess in the company,
he might not be able to take over immediately.
Even if Mr. Cheng An is injured,
his remote command is better than Cheng Yan's.
If you insist on standing in our way,
then don't blame us
for calling a shareholders' meeting to reshuffle the board.
Are you threatening me?
An'an
Mom.
Why are you here?
How are you feeling?
I'm good.
Much better.
It just hurts a little.
Lean back.
Why are you here?
Aren't you busy at the company?
You've heard about what's going on at the company.
The stock plummeted recently,
shareholders are pulling out,
the warehouse is full of returns,
and the production lines are mostly shut down.
Xiao An,
your second brother can't handle things.
The company still needs you.
Mom,
you flatter me too much.
Actually, the day Valley Breeze got into trouble,
I was thinking of contacting you.
But the doctor said
I shouldn't overwork myself.
I have the will, but not the strength.
But,
Valley Breeze is your eldest brother's life's work.
You can't bear to see it ruined, right?
You've always been capable
and full of ideas.
As long as
you're okay,
just make an appearance,
and the staff will feel reassured.
The situation will also stabilize a bit.
You don't have to worry about other things.
After you've recovered,
you can slowly reorganize things.
I know this is hard on you,
but right now,
the situation is really urgent.
I really have no other choice.
Mom.
Since you put it that way,
I'll head back in a few days.
Xiao An.
Hearing that puts my mind completely...
...at ease.
She took the bait.
You took care of me in the hospital these past few days.
I really appreciate it.
Let me give you a ride back to the company on my way.
I should congratulate you first, Little Uncle.
On getting discharged?
Or
on returning to Valley Breeze?
Both.
And...
thank you.
During the incident at the winery that day,
it was the first time I saw you so scared.
I thought I heard you say,
"Dad...
Don't hit me...
Don't hit my dad."
You must have misheard.
That day in the orchard,
I suddenly thought of
when I was attacked by those thugs.
Don't think about it anymore.
From now on,
you won't ever be hurt again.
The top priority
is to recall that batch of adulterated wine and destroy it.
Contact all major media outlets,
and hold a press conference
to apologize for the wine adulteration incident,
and minimize its impact.
At the same time, we must placate the upset fruit farmers.
In addition,
invite the media,
distributors,
and consumers
to visit our brewing process
and livestream the whole event.
Meanwhile, on social media,
release promotional materials
and initiate interactive discussions
to rebuild Valley Breeze's brand image.
This is great! This is great!
This is wonderful!
Mr. Cheng An,
look.
The tide of public opinion has completely turned.
And our stock price
has been rising steadily since morning.
The PR team did a fantastic job this time.
The shareholders are very satisfied
with how you handled this crisis.
Old Li,
did you see?
Valley Breeze's stock price went up again.
This is really great!
Hello?
I've looked into the ice wine issue.
The data in this report is flawed.
The cost of the ice wine business was inflated,
and the market forecast was suppressed.
We both know the potential of the international market.
When Cheng Yan saw a report like this,
he only had one choice.
The ice wine business was cut,
and the fruit farmers' contracts were voided.
The reputation Valley Breeze built in the industry
will also plummet.
Behind the numbers
are living, breathing people.
Sang Luo,
is this what you wanted to see?
I've always trusted
your judgment of the industry.
But this time,
you've really disappointed me.
What's wrong?
Did I do the wrong thing?
If getting revenge means
hurting innocent people...
how am I any different from Lin Wanmei?
You're overthinking this.
Remember, they forced you into this.
Everything you've done is just to protect yourself.
Right now, I can't even tell
if I'm Sang Luo or Ye Xiaowei anymore.
He's right.
I was wrong.
You still have me.
The dirty work you don't want to do,
I'll handle it.
I can't let you bear so much.
And I can't lose myself anymore.
I am absolutely nothing like
the people who hurt me.